Guide to the Tyree Scott Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- NORTHWEST LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT LAW OFFICE (LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT LAW OFFICE) RECORDS, 1961-2005; SERIES 10 (Box-folder 16/32-45/15)
  - Case Files and Legal Papers, 1961-1995; Subseries C (Box-folder 18/33-45/15)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co Ekuk Correspondence re: hiring practices, rehire preference, nepotism, etc., 1975-1976 (Box-folder 34/68)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co Ekuk Correspondence re: job applications, qualifications, race label and identification, hiring practices, nepotism., 1976-1977 (Box-folder 34/69)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co Ekuk Correspondence re: job applications, nepotism, hiring practices, job qualifications, affirmative action, 1976 (Box-folder 34/70)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co Wards Cove Correspondence re: race labelling, housing and messhall quality, discrimination, job opening, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 34/71)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co Wards Cove Correspondence re: race label, hiring practices, nepotism, miscellaneous, 1972 (Box-folder 34/72)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Wards Cove, Kenai, Excursion Inlet, Port Bailey, Correspondence re: race label, nepotism, etc., 1970-1974 (Box-folder 34/73)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak re: terminations, race label, sex discrimination, hiring, boat financing, etc., 1976 (Box-folder 34/74)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak re: recruiting, race label, housing, promotion, nepotism, etc., 1976 (Box-folder 34/75)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak, hiring, nepotism, race labelling, sex segregation, promotions, dispatch, termination, job duties, etc., 1976 (Box-folder 34/76)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak, training, promotions, recommendations, job openings, Affirmative Action, etc., 1976 (Box-folder 34/77)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak and others, re: race label, job qualifications, 1970 (Box-folder 34/78)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak re: hiring, race labelling, recruiting, immigration, dispatching women, 1971 (Box-folder 34/79)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak hiring, L.37 Contract, sex segregation, race label, 1971 (Box-folder 34/80)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak re: hiring, race label, L.37 contract, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 34/81)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak terminations, race label, job duties, L.37 contract, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 34/82)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak re: race label, hiring, housing, boat charter, 1973 (Box-folder 34/83)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak re: terminations, promotions, nepotism, affirmative action, etc., 1972-1974 (Box-folder 34/84)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Alitak hiring, law suit, union delegate report, job duties, rehiring, nepotism, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 34/85)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Alitak; Union dues, nepotism, race label, Affirmative Action, Hiring/Housing, 1975 (Box-folder 34/86)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Other Canneries, nepotism, hiring, job duties, housing quality, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 34/87)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Alitak & others race label, recruiting, hiring, nepotism, 1972 (Box-folder 34/88)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Chignik- Most Recent Documents, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 34/89)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Moser Bay- Most Recent Documents, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 34/90)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Red Salmon- Most Recent Documents, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 34/91)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Ekuk- Most Recent Documents, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 34/92)
    - Atonio v. Ward Cove Packing Co., EEOC Compliance Review Documents, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 34/93)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Port Bailey- Most Recent Documents, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 34/94)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Wards Cove- Recent Documents, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 34/95)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Ketchikan- Recent Documents, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 34/96)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Alitak- Most Recent Documents, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 34/97)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Unfiled Exhibits (1 of 2), 1972-1977 (Box-folder 34/98)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Unfiled Exhibits (2 of 2), 1972-1977 (Box-folder 34/99)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., EEOC Compliance Reviews (1 of 2), 1972-1977 (Box-folder 34/100)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., EEOC Compliance Reviews (2 of 2), 1972-1977 (Box-folder 35/1)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Chris Allegaert (1 of 2), 1980-1982 (Box-folder 35/2)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Chris Allegaert (2 of 2), 1980-1982 (Box-folder 35/3)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Witness File- Chris Allegaert, 1981 (Box-folder 35/4)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Larry de France Witness File, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 35/5)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Witness File-Michael Schwiger, 1982 (Box-folder 35/6)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Deposition of Alec W. Brindle, 1974 (Box-folder 35/7)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Witness File-Gene Navarro, 1981 (Box-folder 35/8)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Witness File- Gene Silberberg, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 35/9)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Witness File- Jill Henderson, 1978 (Box-folder 35/10)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Shirley J. Smith Deposition, 1981 (Box-folder 35/11)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Witness File- Joe Ancheta, 1980 (Box-folder 35/12)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Witness File- Kim Tsujii, 1980 (Box-folder 35/13)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Deposition of John Bozanich, 1970 (Box-folder 35/14)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Greg Sotello, 1980 (Box-folder 35/15)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Ambrosia Pascua, 1980 (Box-folder 35/16)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Joe Brindle, 1979? (Box-folder 35/17)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Tom Catell, 1980 (Box-folder 35/18)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Randall Milholland, 1980 (Box-folder 35/19)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - William Ancheta, 1980 (Box-folder 35/20)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Salvador del Fierro Sr., 1976-1980 (Box-folder 35/21)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Larry DeFrance (all resumes), 1980 (Box-folder 35/22)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness File - Roger Parker, 1980-1982 (Box-folder 35/23)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Cheryle R. Dittner, 1980 (Box-folder 35/24)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file, Deposition and Testimony - Arthur Hippler (contains book research on Filipino-Americans, Asian Americans, North Alaska Eskimo, Athabascans, etc) File 1 of 2, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 35/25)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file, Deposition and Testimony - Arthur Hippler (contains book research on Filipino-Americans, Asian Americans, North Alaska Eskimo, Athabascans, etc) File 2 of 2, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 35/26)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Arthur Hippler, 1980 (Box-folder 35/27)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Albert Rees, 1980 (Box-folder 35/28)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Arthur Hippler, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 35/29)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Ben Tabayonon, 1980 (Box-folder 35/30)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Cef Decaney Sr., 1980 (Box-folder 35/31)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Kari Berger, 1978 (Box-folder 35/32)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Rex Shelton, 1980 (Box-folder 35/33)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Larry DeFrance Interview Notes. File 1 of 2, 1980 (Box-folder 35/34)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Larry DeFrance Interview Notes. File 2 of 2, 1980 (Box-folder 35/35)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Gene Allen Viernes, 1981 (Box-folder 35/36)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Stan Viernes, 1980 (Box-folder 35/37)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co.Witness file - William R. Pascua, 1980 (Box-folder 35/38)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition Of Frank Atonio, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 35/39)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - William "Ted" Pascua, 1980 (Box-folder 35/40)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Joaquin Arruiza, 1981 (Box-folder 35/41)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Philip Fujii, 1980 (Box-folder 35/42)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Eugene Baclig, 1980 (Box-folder 35/43)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Alan Lew, 1981 (Box-folder 35/44)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Donald Wise, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 35/45)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Lester Kuramoto, 1981 (Box-folder 35/46)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Albert Rees, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 35/47)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Marvin Snyder, 1974 (Box-folder 36/1)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Mervin Lessley, 1970-1978 (Box-folder 36/2)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of John Jorgensen, 1970 (Box-folder 36/3)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Wallace Mullis, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box-folder 36/4)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Randy del Fierro, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 36/5)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Albert Abuan, 1981 (Box-folder 36/6)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Clarke Kido, 1975-1980 (Box-folder 36/7)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Russel Rohrer, circa 1970s (Box-folder 36/8)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - Sylvestre Tangalan, 1980 (Box-folder 36/9)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Winn F. Brindle, circa 1970s (Box-folder 36/10)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Deposition of Ray Landry, 1973 (Box-folder 36/11)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Witness file - James Farrell, 1981 (Box-folder 36/12)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Settlement Sheets (CW) Ekuk, 1970 (Box-folder 36/13)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Settlement Sheets (CW) Ekuk, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 36/14)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Settlement Sheets (CW) Ekuk, 1970 (Box-folder 36/15)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Settlement Sheets (CW) Ekuk, 1974 (Box-folder 36/16)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Settlement Sheets (CW) Ekuk, 1975 (Box-folder 36/17)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Settlement Sheets (CW) Ekuk, 1975 (Box-folder 36/18)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Settlement Sheets (K) Wards Cove, 1974 (Box-folder 36/19)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Settlement Sheets (K) Wards Cove, 1974 (Box-folder 36/20)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Settlement Sheets (K) Wards Cove, 1975 (Box-folder 36/21)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Seine Settlement Sheets (CW) Alitak, 1974 (Box-folder 36/22)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Seine Settlement Sheets (CW) Alitak File 1 of 2, 1974 (Box-folder 36/23)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Seine Settlement Sheets (CW) Alitak File 2 of 2, 1974 (Box-folder 36/24)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Seine Settlement Sheets (CW) Alitak, 1970 (Box-folder 36/25)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Settlement Sheets (CW) Alitak File 1 of 2, 1970 (Box-folder 36/26)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Settlement Sheets (CW) Alitak File 2 of 2, 1970 (Box-folder 36/27)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Northwest Labor and Employment Law Office Correspondence, 1989 (Box-folder 36/28)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Supreme Court of the United States Reports, 1988-1989 (Box-folder 36/29)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Misc. including letters of hiring, signing work registers, Local #7, Joint Apprenticeship Training Committee, Equal Employment Opportunity, Affirmative Action, Deposition of Michael George Strigen, and hiring hall list, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 36/30)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Research documents including Index of Industries and Occupations, Alaska Fishery and Fur-Seal Industries, Fisheries Management, and note regarding Deposition of Slime Domingo, 1974 (Box-folder 36/31)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Settlement Statements (CW) Alitak, 1975 (Box-folder 36/32)
    - Equal Employment Opportunity v. Local 86, International Association of Bridge, Structural and Ornamental and Reinforced Ironworkers, et. al. including exhibits, 1979 (Box-folder 36/33)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Summary of Statistical Tests for Case Red Salmon Plaintiff Theory, All Hires 1971-1980, Referenced to case all but Ice Cape File 1 of 5 (Box-folder 37/1)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Summary of Statistical Tests for Case Red Salmon Plaintiff Theory, All Hires 1971-1980, Referenced to case all but Ice Cape File 2 of 5 (Box-folder 37/2)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Summary of Statistical Tests for Case Red Salmon Plaintiff Theory, All Hires 1971-1980, Referenced to case all but Ice Cape File 3 of 5 (Box-folder 37/3)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Summary of Statistical Tests for Case Red Salmon Plaintiff Theory, All Hires 1971-1980, Referenced to case all but Ice Cape File 4 of 5 (Box-folder 37/4)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Summary of Statistical Tests for Case Red Salmon Plaintiff Theory, All Hires 1971-1980, Referenced to case all but Ice Cape File 5 of 5 (Box-folder 37/5)
    - Alyeska Case - Preliminaries, 1975 (Box-folder 37/6)
    - Walker v. Marshall - Pleadings I, File 1 of 2, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 37/7)
    - Walker v. Marshall - Pleadings I, File 2 of 2, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 37/8)
    - Gene Viernes - Oral History Project, 1980 (Box-folder 37/9)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. - Pleadings XXIX, File 1 of 2, 1981 (Box-folder 38/1)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. - Pleadings XXIX, File 2 of 2, 1981 (Box-folder 38/2)
    - United Construction Workers Association (UCWA) v. Cochran Electric - Correspondence, 1980 (Box-folder 38/3)
    - Local 86 Expansion, Electrical Workers Local 46, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 38/4)
    - Comment on Justice Department's Class Action Reform Proposal, 1972-1978 (Box-folder 38/5)
    - Agreement Between Puget Sound Chapter National Electrical Contractors Association and Local Union 46 International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers, 1969-1971 (Box-folder 38/6)
    - ???AHTCH Haes Dr. Fire, Alaska Cannery Workers Association (ACWA), 1974 (Box-folder 38/7)
    - Alaska Cannery Workers Association (ACWA) v. Castle & Cooke, et. al. - Office of Federal Contract Compliance (OFCCP) Complaint, 1978 (Box-folder 38/8)
    - Sir Amos (Adv. Sea-Land Service, Inc.), 1979 (Box-folder 38/9)
    - Gregory Buford - Apprenticeship Cancellation, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 38/10)
    - Cecil McCormack (Adv. Local 46) International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), 1968-1978 (Box-folder 38/11)
    - Temporary Wiring - United Construction Workers Association (UCWA), 1974 (Box-folder 38/12)
    - Labor Agreement Between Associated General Contractors of America, Inc. and The Washington and Northern Idaho District Council of Laborers, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 38/13)
    - Boykin & Mallet Labor Injunction, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 38/14)
    - American Friends Service Committee, Inc. (AFSC) Affirmative Action Plan - Michael Simmons, 1977 (Box-folder 38/15)
    - Tyree Scott v. Local 46, 1977 (Box-folder 38/16)
    - Alaska Cannery Workers Association (ACWA) v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) - Office of Federal Contract Compliance (OFCCP) Complaint, 1974-1979 (Box-folder 38/17)
    - George Richardson - Adv. Wright-Shuchart-Harbor; Local 313, Teamsters; AGC, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 38/18)
    - United Construction Workers Association (UCWA) v. John Dunlop, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 38/19)
    - Cannery Cases - General Future of Industry, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 38/20)
    - Clovis Campbell v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) - Pleading File No. 1, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 38/21)
    - Kenworth Planning File (AAA), 1977 (Box-folder 38/22)
    - Lawsuit re: Coffee Breaks - Preliminary Research, 1976 (Box-folder 38/23)
    - E.O. 11246 Regulations - Comment, 1977 (Box-folder 38/24)
    - Barbara Jacobsen & Jan Darger - Adv. Century Construction Co., 1978 (Box-folder 38/25)
    - Clovis Campbell, 1974 (Box-folder 38/26)
    - Advocates for Women v. Marshall, 1977 (Box-folder 38/27)
    - Steve Lock - Adv. Hoffman Construction Co., Coluccio Construction Co., H.S. Lease Construction Co., Sellen Construction Co., 1977-1978 (Box-folder 38/28)
    - Dillard Craven - Adv. American Airlines; Local 514, Transport Workers Union, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 38/29)
    - Susan Helf - Payroll, 1980 (Box-folder 38/30)
    - Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO) 1974 Annual Board of Directors Meeting (Box-folder 38/31)
    - Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO) Charitable Solicitation Act, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 38/32)
    - Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO) Lease - Tenancy 105 14th Avenue, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 38/33)
    - Law Student Work Study Vouchers, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 38/34)
    - University of Washington Work Study Correspondence, 1978 (Box-folder 38/35)
    - Independent Minority Truckers & Equipment Operators Association - Contract Renewal, Undated (Box-folder 38/36)
    - Walker v. Marshall Correspondence, 1978 (Box-folder 38/37)
    - Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO) Employment Security, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 38/38)
    - Roger Evans - Adv. Port of Seattle, 1977 (Box-folder 38/39)
    - Donna Linn - Adv. Local 46, International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers (IBEW), JAC, National Electrical Control Association (NECA), 1977-1980 (Box-folder 38/40)
    - Cheryl Crawford - Adv. Local 46, IBEW, JATC, NECA, 1977 (Box-folder 38/41)
    - Funding Rejections, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 38/42)
    - Fundraising Materials, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 38/43)
    - Northwest Labor and Employment Law Office (LELO) Funding Proposals, 1976 (Box-folder 39/1)
    - Funding III, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 39/2)
    - Funding II, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 39/3)
    - Fundraising - Miscellaneous Materials, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 39/4)
    - Fundraising - Second Proposal, Working File, 1978 (Box-folder 39/5)
    - Fundraising Trip 5/27/1978 (Box-folder 39/6)
    - Akbar Fund, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 39/7)
    - American Friends Service Committee, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 39/8)
    - Archdiocese Stewardship Fund, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 39/9)
    - Asian Law Caucus, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 39/10)
    - ATR - A Territory Resource, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 39/11)
    - Board for Homeland Ministries - United Church of Christ, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 39/12)
    - The Cambium Fund, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 39/13)
    - Campaign for Human Development, File 1 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 39/14)
    - Campaign for Human Development, File 2 of 2, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 39/15)
    - Campaign for Human Development 1/19/76, File 1 of 2, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 39/16)
    - Campaign for Human Development 1/19/76, File 2 of 2, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 39/17)
    - Haas Memorial Fund, 1975 (Box-folder 39/18)
    - Interreligious Foundation for Community Organization, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 39/19)
    - Laras Fund, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 39/20)
    - Mott Foundation, 1977 (Box-folder 39/21)
    - National Commission on Hispanic Affairs, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 39/22)
    - National Committee on the Self-Development of People, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 39/23)
    - National Lawyers Guild Loan, 1980 (Box-folder 39/24)
    - New World Foundation, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 39/25)
    - Norman Foundation, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 39/26)
    - Playboy Foundation, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 39/27)
    - Rabinowitz Foundation, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 39/28)
    - The Seed Fund, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 39/29)
    - Shalan Foundation, 1974-1978 (Box-folder 39/30)
    - Campaign for Human Development, October 1977 (Box-folder 39/31)
    - Commission on Racial Justice - United Church of Christ, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 39/32)
    - Community Action and Human Development, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 39/33)
    - Coalition for Human Needs - Episcopal Church, 1979 (Box-folder 39/34)
    - Commission on Religion & Race - United Methodist Church, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 39/35)
    - Council for Public Interest Law, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 40/1)
    - Cummins Engine Foundation, 1973-1978 (Box-folder 40/2)
    - The Curtis Foundation, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 40/3)
    - Emergency Fund for Legal Aid, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 40/4)
    - Ferry Family & DJB Foundation, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 40/5)
    - Fund for Class Action Costs, 1975-1981 (Box-folder 40/6)
    - Japanese American Citizens League, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 40/7)
    - Charles H. Revson Foundation, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 40/8)
    - Southwest LELO Fundraising, 1978 (Box-folder 40/9)
    - Stern Fund, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 40/10)
    - Third World Fund, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 40/11)
    - United Ministries - Reverend Frank Kelsey, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 40/12)
    - Vanguard Foundation, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 40/13)
    - Unitarian Church - Veatch, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 40/14)
    - Weiss, Jonathan A. - Legal Services for the Elderly Poor, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 40/15)
    - Weyerhaeuser Foundation, 1977 (Box-folder 40/16)
    - Wright Charitable Trust, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 40/17)
    - The Youth Project, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 40/18)
    - New England Fish Company (NEFCO) / Fidalgo - John Lynn, 1971 (Box-folder 40/19)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) / Fidalgo - Motion to Compel on Tax Issue, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 40/20)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) / Fidalgo - Deposition Notes, 1976 (Box-folder 40/21)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) / Fidalgo - Our Up-Date of Their Discovery - Working File, 1976 (Box-folder 40/22)
    - February 1976, Depositions, Ketchikan, AL. Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) / Fidalgo (Box-folder 40/23)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) / Fidalgo - Honorato Rapada Interview, 1979 (Box-folder 40/24)
    - UFWA v. Del Monte - Working Papers in Opp to Motion to Compel, 1978 (Box-folder 40/25)
    - United Farm Workers (UFW) v. Del Monte, et. al. Pleadings II 9/78, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 40/26)
    - United Farm Workers (UFW) v. Del Monte, et. al. Pleadings I, 1978 (Box-folder 40/27)
    - United Farm Workers (UFW) v. Del Monte, et. al. Correspondence, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 40/28)
    - Women in Trades v. Spellman, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 40/29)
    - United Farm Workers (UFW) v. Del Monte - Extra Pleadings, File 1 of 2, 1978 (Box-folder 40/30)
    - United Farm Workers (UFW) v. Del Monte - Extra Pleadings, File 2 of 2, 1978 (Box-folder 40/31)
    - Plaintiff's Counsel, File 1 of 2, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 40/32)
    - Plaintiff's Counsel, File 2 of 2, 1975 (Box-folder 40/33)
    - Plaintiff's Counsel - Trial Brief Notes/Materials, 1976 (Box-folder 40/34)
    - Plaintiff's Counsel - Local 302 Interrogs, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 40/35)
    - Plaintiff's Counsel - Local 302 Operating Engineers, et. al., 1975-1976 (Box-folder 40/36)
    - Plaintiff's Counsel - Local 302 Trial Brief, 1976 (Box-folder 40/37)
    - Plaintiff's Counsel - Local 302, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 40/38)
    - Plaintiff's Counsel - Personal, circa 1980s (Box-folder 40/39)
    - Women in Trades, et. al. v. John D. Spellman, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 40/40)